(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T13:12:10.182623",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ローソンへお越しの皆さん
To everyone visiting Lawson,
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson campaign confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These 6 members are appearing!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details releasing Monday, March 9!
推しのバンドブースも大人気！
The Oshi band booths are super popular too!
注目の新商品も初公開！
Highly anticipated new merchandise revealed!
オリジナルフレームで撮影！あなただけのカードデザイン！！
Take photos with an original frame! Your own card design!!
発売前のウエハースシリーズデザイン！？ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Pre-release wafer designs!? Get a limited card at the booth!
and MOREの公開も決定！
And MORE announcements confirmed!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream,
想像できないような
beyond imagination,
想いになったんだ
it became feelings.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost,
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
A little bit of anxiety, too,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll blow it all away.
果てない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey
駆けてる途中に
that we are running through,
もう困難もあるでしょう
there are bound to be difficulties,
それも力に変えて
we'll turn those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねぇ、夢では終われない
hey, we can't end it just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine just like myself.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
hey, is my treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
taking hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
A sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
trying to disturb our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve won't waver.
ちゃんとしないと！って背中
A push on the back saying 'Do it right!'
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね
We must cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”はないからさ
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どこから始めればいいか迷って
wondering where best to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
we formed a circle and found step by step
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream nothing else can replace.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the incomplete,
想いは一つだ
our feelings are one.
僅かな希望でも
Even with a glimmer of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always
馬鹿にされても
be laughed at, but
信じたい！
we want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, thank you isn't enough,
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
hey, our feelings are overflowing,
ずっと一緒だよ！
we'll always be together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねぇ、夢では終われない
hey, we can't end it just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine just like myself.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
hey, is my treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
taking hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone,
何度でも立ち上がってさ
standing up again and again,
笑い合っていたい
wanting to laugh together.
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
That's our wish, everyone, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream,
想像できないような
beyond imagination,
想いになったんだ
it became feelings.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost,
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
A little bit of anxiety, too,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll blow it all away.
果てない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey
駆けてる途中に
that we are running through,
もう困難もあるでしょう
there are bound to be difficulties,
それも力に変えて
we'll turn those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were there,
ねぇ、夢では終われない
hey, we can't end it just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine just like myself.
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
hey, is my treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
taking hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going further!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ hey！！
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
A sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
trying to disturb our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
we swore on that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve won't waver.
ちゃんとしないと！って背中
A push on the back saying 'Do it right!'
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね
We must cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”はないからさ
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どこから始めればいいか迷って
wondering where best to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
we formed a circle and found step by step
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream nothing else can replace.
ridin' on dreams
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Thanking you over and over,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a tiny dream,
想像できないような
Into something beyond imagination,
想いになったんだな
It became a feeling.
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll just blow it away.
果てしない旅路を今
This endless journey right now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
Surely has hardships along the way,
それも力に変えて
Turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
We'll press forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
We won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's push through the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you,
ねえ、宝物だから
Is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an uncharted world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
Tries to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだよ
We swore on that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve will not waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
Our backs saying "We've gotta do it!",
明日の橋になる
Will become the bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね
We have to cherish things more,
“あたりまえ”はないから
Because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat,
どこから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling over where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Finding it step by step as a circle,
何にも代えられない夢だ
A dream that cannot be replaced.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even our incompleteness,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with the slimmest hope,
僕と君でずっと
You and I will always...
馬鹿にされても
Even if mocked,
信じたい！
We want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
A "thank you" isn't enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れきいちゃうんだよ
My feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Thanking you over and over,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a tiny dream,
想像できないような
Into something beyond imagination,
想いになったんだな
It became a feeling.
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll just blow it away.
果てしない旅路を今
This endless journey right now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
Surely has hardships along the way,
それも力に変えて
Turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
We'll press forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
We won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's push through the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you,
ねえ、宝物だから
Is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an uncharted world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
Tries to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだよ
We swore on that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve will not waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
Our backs saying "We've gotta do it!",
明日の橋になる
Will become the bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしないとね
We have to cherish things more,
“あたりまえ”はないから
Because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat,
どこから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling over where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Finding it step by step as a circle,
何にも代えられない夢だ
A dream that cannot be replaced.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even our incompleteness,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with the slimmest hope,
僕と君でずっと
You and I will always...
馬鹿にされても
Even if mocked,
信じたい！
We want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
A "thank you" isn't enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れきいちゃうんだよ
My feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
We won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's push through the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you...
会場にいる同志諸君！Stage3を震わせる！！！応援を！！！
Comrades in the venue! Make Stage3 shake! Give your support!!!
ぺこたん 6年間ありがとう！！
Pekotan, thank you for 6 years!!
輪堂788 RAV4
Rindo 788 RAV4
るーなたんすき♡
I love you, Runatan♡
切って！
Cut it!
AZKi's LOCATION!〜で鹿児島の温泉入りにきて！
Come soak in Kagoshima's hot springs at AZKi's LOCATION!
夢を叶えるためにある Yagoo
Yagoo, here to make dreams come true
あずいろはいいぞ。
Azu-iro is the best.
牛丼はデザート
Gyudon is dessert
から、！オラ
From... Ora!
AZKi
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
パヴォリア・レイネ
Pavolia Reine
IRyS
ハコス・ベールズ
Hakos Baelz
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
響咲リオナ
Isaki Riona
虎金妃笑虎
Koganei Niko
水宮枢
Mizumiya Su
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
々々羅々ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you so many times
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
right now!
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop on!
Ridin' on Dreams
ああ小さな夢から
From such a small dream,
想像できないような想いになったんだ
into feelings we couldn't even imagine,
わくわく止まらない！
our excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら絆が舵になる
No matter how many times we get lost, our bonds become our rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We'll blow away even a little bit of anxiety!
険しい旅路を今、軽いでる途中に困難もあるでしょ
As we journey on this rugged road, there are bound to be difficulties,
それも力に変えて一緒に進むんだよ！
but we'll turn them into strength and move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves together
"らしく"輝いていたい
Wanting to shine "our own way"
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is our greatest treasure
手を取り合い声を掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an uncharted world with no map at all,
まだまだ行こう！
we can still keep going!
Ridin' on Dreams
急な風が僕らの行く先乱そうとも
Even if sudden winds try to disturb our path,
あの日誓ったんだ覚悟は揺るがない
we swore on that day our resolve won't waver.
きちんとしないと！って背中
"You've got to do it right!"—that push on the back
明日への橋になるもっと大事にしないとね
becomes a bridge to tomorrow, we have to cherish it even more.
"あたりまえ"はないから小さな船から始まるストーリー
There's no such thing as taking things for granted, starting from a small boat.
どこから始めたらいいか悩んで少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Wondering where to start, little by little we formed a circle and found
何にも代わりえない夢だ
a dream that cannot be replaced by anything else.
未完成も愛して想いは一つだ
Loving even our incomplete selves, our feelings are one.
僅かな希望でも僕と君でずっと
Even with just a glimmer of hope, you and I forever...
馬鹿にされても信じたい！
Even if we're mocked, we want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, our feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
雨上がりの水溜まり浮かぶ
Puddles floating after the rain
曇り顔がそっと笑った
A cloudy face softly smiled
気付いたら隣にいるんだ
Before I knew it, you were by my side
言葉なんてもういらないよ
Words are no longer needed,
これからもそうさ
and it will be like that from now on too.
誰だって泣いたり転んだり
No matter who you are, there are times when you cry, fall,
凹むこともあるけれど
and get depressed,
そんなこと忘れてワクワクしたいのさ
But I want to forget all that and get excited.
進め 進め もっと先へ
Advance, advance, further ahead
虹の向こうまで
To the other side of the rainbow
君と手をつないでいられたら
If I can hold hands with you
どこへだって行けるね
We can go anywhere
鳴らせ 鳴らせ 祝福の音
Ring, ring, the sound of blessing
空に響き渡れ
Resound across the sky
見たことない 景色探しに行こう
Let's go search for scenery we've never seen before
So Happy Magic
この素晴らしい世界で
In this wonderful world
カバンいっぱいにつめ込んだ荷物
Luggage packed full in a bag
空っぽにして飛び出せば
If you empty it and jump out
ここがスタートさ
This is the start
この先 いくつの困難に
No matter how many difficulties
行く手を阻まれても
Try to block your path ahead
まとめて吹き飛ばす 強さがあるでしょ？ほら
We have the strength to blow them all away, right? Look
走れ 走れ 限界超え
Run, run, beyond our limits
遥か彼方まで
To the far horizon
曖昧な気持ちじゃ
With ambiguous feelings
何だって叶いはしないさ
Nothing will ever come true
掴み 掴み 一番星
Catch, catch, the brightest star
空に手を伸ばして
Stretch your hand toward the sky
まだ知らない 仲間と巡り会う
Encounter new friends you don't know yet
So Happy Magic
信じていれば叶うよ
If you believe, it will come true
大切なものは きっと未来にあるんだ
What is precious is surely in the future
だから 振り返らなくていいじゃない
So you don't need to look back
不安はいつしか 大きなドキドキに変わるから
Anxiety will eventually turn into great excitement
歌おう 笑おう
Let's sing, let's laugh
進め 進め もっと先へ
Advance, advance, further ahead
虹の向こうまで
To the other side of the rainbow
追い風を引き連れ
Pulling along a tailwind,
せーので走り出せ
ready, set, start running
鳴らせ 鳴らせ 祝福の音
Ring, ring, the sound of blessing
空に響き渡れ
Resound across the sky
さあ 始めよう 終わらない冒険を
Now, let's begin an endless adventure
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 輝くんだよ
Sunny, sunny, sunny, shining brightly
呼び合う声を合図に
With voices calling out to each other as a signal
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 探しに行く
Sunny, sunny, sunny, going to search for it
スタートは何度だって
The start is however many times we want
...
ひとりごと づくった
Mumbling to myself
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just wanted to start and ran off
遠く 暗がりで止まった
Stopped in the distant darkness
それは
That was...
眩しすぎた名前
A name that was too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思い出
That was too tender of a memory
もっと 心地つけと手をとばした
I wanted to feel more at ease and reached out my hand
思いがけず結び合った ほら今
Unexpectedly tied together, look, right now
迷い子は
The lost children
僕らだった
Were the two of us
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ 輝くんだよ
Sunny, sunny, sunny, shining brightly
悔しさも愛おしさも 全ておいで
Regret and endearment, let them all come
風邪気味羽根飛び立てさ
Catch a cold, spread your wings and take flight
ささやかな日常は 光 終わりなききざし
The quiet daily life is light, an endless omen
君を
You...
見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Can hold your head high about finding
僕らから これから
From us, from now on
あー ぐらり 晴れ 晴れ
Ah, wobbling, sunny, sunny
晴れ 晴れ 晴れ
Sunny, sunny, sunny
まだ 頼りないよかも
It's still unreliable perhaps
歌を 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
There's nothing to be ashamed of about singing
誰も 解けない いましめに
A spell that no one can break
いつか また会えを まじない
A spell to meet again someday
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that started from zero on that day
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を 合図に
It's time to take the stage.
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにいく ズタートは何回だって
A new journey awaits.
パレード、パレード、パレード
Parade, parade, parade!
美しくんだよ
It's shining bright!
夜はきらめく
The night glimmers.
またとない空
Again to the empty sky.
君とあることさ
Being with you.
現在（いま）をひけば
The present moment.
当たり前じゃないか
It's not taken for granted!
パレード、パレード、パレード
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It's shining bright!
君だ、僕が
You and I.
輝くんだよ
It's shining bright!
おいで！
Come on over!
飛び込んでさ
Jump in!
終わりなき兆し
A never-ending sign.
素敵なスタートさ
A wonderful start!
パレード、パレード、パレード
Parade, parade, parade!
Our bright parade!
ステージ3、行くよ！
Stage 3, let's go!
あの太陽よりもっと高く
Reaching higher than that sun,
手を伸ばして
I stretch out my hands!
長く伸ばした
Stretching far across
季節色の影の上を
The seasonal shadows,
騒がしい足跡で飾って
Adorning them with noisy footsteps,
ワクワクする方へ向かおうか
Let's head toward the excitement!
決められた未来と逆の景色ばっか
Trying to go against the fixed future,
行こうとしている 間違ってないか？
Am I mistaken?
がっかりしてないか？
Am I wrong?
散々迷って また今日に立っていた
After wandering around, I'm back here today.
誰も歩かない 道の先で煙んだ声がする
At the end of a path no one walks,
誰も気づけない 予想外の明日は 今閃いちゃったんだ！
An unexpected tomorrow has suddenly started sparkling!
どうしよう！
What should I do?
まだまだ頭が冴えていく
My mind is still clearing up.
皆が変わっていると笑った毎日が
Every day I laughed at for being different
突然特別になるから
Suddenly becomes special,
今から世界に恋にしに行こう
So let's go fall in love with the world right now!
真っ直ぐ昇ったまま
Reaching past the straight, rising,
消えない太陽に手を伸ばして
Unfading sun!
覚えてるんだ
I remember now.
最初は隠してた癖も
Even the habits I used to hide,
恥ずかしくて語れない夢も
And the embarrassing dreams I couldn't speak of,
一つ一つは特別に見えなくても
Even if they don't seem special individually,
重なり合ってほら 今色めいた
When they overlap, they start to shine today!
間違っていないよ
There's no mistake!
がっかりしてないよ
There's no disappointment!
散々な道が 一番楽しいんだ！
A scattered path is the most fun after all!
なんだろう
I wonder why,
ちょっとだけ頭がズレていく
My head is going just a little off-track.
皆と違っていると凹んだ毎日が
The days I felt down for being different from everyone
きっと最高になるから
Are bound to become the best,
今から世界をハグしに行こう
So let's go give the world a hug right now!
すっかり昇ったまま 消えない太陽も追い抜かして
Passing right past that un-fading sun!
どうしよう！
How about that?
しのびない！I get the feeling
Can't bear it! I get the feeling
死ぬまでやりな
Do it till you die
君の言うこの140文字の流行語は
The 140-character buzzwords you say
待ちくたびれてないよ
I'm not tired of waiting
がっかりしないよ
I'm not disappointed at all
さんざんな道が一番楽しいな
The roughest path is the most fun of all
なんだろう ちょっとだけ頭がズレていく
I wonder why... my head's slipping just a little bit
みんなと違ってるって凹んだ毎日が
Every day I felt down about being different from everyone else
きっと最高になるから 今から世界を剥がしに行こう
Will surely become the best, so let's go strip away the world right now
しっかり登ったまま消えない太陽を
The un-fading sun climbing steadily high
追い抜いて先頭しよう
Let's outrun it and take the lead
まだまだお供を連れて行く
Bringing even more companions along
みんなと変わってるって笑った毎日が
Every day people laughed at me for being different
突然とびきりないから 今すぐ世界に恋しに行こう
Won't suddenly be extraordinary, so let's go fall in love with the world right now
あの空の枠外さに埋まっちゃうくらいに
To the point of getting buried in that sky's boundless space
手を伸ばして
Reaching out my hands...
しのびない！I get the feeling
Can't bear it! I get the feeling
Will you end my pain?
Will you take my life?
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Say things I never wanted to say
24/7, can't please y'all, livin' and dyin' by day
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Win, stand, beat until it's Sunday
Hold it, so frustrated, you know I can't do it no more
No, goddamn, do I got hair? You not caring, can't be that loud
Yeah, live, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you right now
No, I'm never, never, though your ideals, oh ideals
That you're screaming in my ear, I'm just so broken down, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Your ideals, oh ideals, that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken down, yeah, never, never, never
Never gonna figure it out
Won't stop me, never gonna figure it out
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
You and me don't know what I just don't know, mommy, you're the hurry, I know a little bit
That you know I'm just making light of it, put me inside a penance bin of your perfection, correction
Tearing me down, am I what you wanted?
Now don't tell me what to do, what to say, think about everything, but then you rub it in
Tell you everything, so well-being, so bad, watch what that is
Yeah, live, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you right now
No, I'm never, never, though your ideals, oh ideals
That you're screaming in my ear, I'm just so broken down, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out, won't stop me
Never gonna figure it out, your ideals, oh ideals
That you're screaming in my ear, I'm just so broken down, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Don't stumble on platostatic
I like it, I'll wake it, you're brutal, you're fell, you're dirty temp and put it out
I saw all what to meet your harsh cries to you, yeah
Too bad I'm never gonna... I'm never gonna fit
Ah, never, never, never gonna figure it out
Yeah, live, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you right now
No, I'm never, never, though your ideals, oh ideals
That you're screaming in my ear, I'm just so broken down, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out, won't stop me
Never gonna figure it out, oh stop me, I'll never figure it out
Won't stop me, I'll never figure it out
Never, never, never going anywhere else!
コマせる？白銀ノエルです！
I'm Noel Shirogane!
みんな、盛り上がっていくぞ！
Everyone, let's get hyped up!
終わらない 終わらない
It never ends, it never ends,
仕事の山積み 終わらない
A mountain of work never ends.
止まらない 止まらない
It won't stop, it won't stop,
それでも時間は止まらない
Even so, time doesn't stop.
ヘッドヘッド 溜まり溜まったヘッド
Head to head, accumulated head,
失点バット 打ち返すバット
Strike out bat, hitting back bat,
コンボ メンタル 金属バット
Combo mental, metal bat.
今日も手一杯 今日も手一杯
Overflowing today too, overflowing today too.
のーもあ無茶ぶり ぎみぎみジューシー
No more unreasonable demands, juicy.
細え見たい 細え見たい
So slender, so slender,
ため息ふれすでえむぴすっからかん
Sighing fresh-day, pencil empty.
自分自身に 厳しすぎちゃう
Too harsh on yourself.
すぐさまヘラヘラ 劣等生
Instantly flailing, bottom student.
自分自身と しっかり向き合う
Facing yourself properly.
一番必要なものは テレビ愛
The most necessary thing is TV love.
ご都合主義ちょうだい てんてこ舞いな リズムに バイバイしちゃえ
Give me convenienceism, say bye-bye to frantic rhythms.
ドレミファノートに ごろり ぎゅーぎゅー詰めちゃダメ もう一回！
Don't stuff solfege notes rolling around tightly, one more time!
トレビアン ごくおびちょうだい てんてこ舞いな リズムに バイバイしちゃえ
Tres bien, give me a Gokou obi, say bye-bye to frantic rhythm.
ドレミファノートに ごろり ぎゅーぎゅー詰めちゃどんどんふりいだむ
Don't stuff solfege notes rolling around tightly, freedom!
ぎゅーぎゅー詰めちゃダメ どんどん不意に堕ちる
Don't stuff it too tight, suddenly falling in.
ぎゅーぎゅー詰めればどんどん好きになる
Stuff it tight and you'll love it more and more.
ぎゅっ！どん！ぎゅっ！どん！どん！
Gyu! Don! Gyu! Don! Don!
ぎゅっ！どん！ぎゅっと知ってドン！
Gyu! Don! Know it tight and don!
さあさぎゅっどん だぎゅっどん 一緒に食べよう
Come on, gyudon, gyudon, let's eat together.
キミとなかよく カーニバル！
Carnival with you!
とろとろチューワンは
The torotoro chu-wan is
ホロリお肉 お肉
Horori meat, meat.
つまんじゃダメ
Don't pinch.
全部食べたら 褒めちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you.
なでなで よしよし ちゅー ちゅーちゅー
Nade-nade, yoshi-yoshi, chu-chu-chu.
あぴゃ あぴゃ あぴゃぴゃ あぴゃぴゃ
Apya apya apya...
あぴゃ あぴゃ あぴゃぴゃ あぴゃぴゃ 洗脳中
Brainwashing in progress...
洗脳開始！
Brainwashing start!
すきすきだいちゅきー！
I love you so much!
らびゅらびゅらびゅ 洗脳中～
Love you, love you, brainwashing in progress.
むちむちむち 責めちゃダメ～
Muchi-muchi, don't tease me.
よくできました ほっぺにちゅ～！
Good job, a kiss on the cheek!
ところが全然足りません
However, it's not enough at all.
それでも全然足りません
Even so, it's not enough at all.
まだまだ全然足りないの
Still not enough at all.
ドキがむねむね 止まらない！
Heart is pounding nonstop!
牛丼を食べる時は お口でふーふーってしてって
When eating gyudon, blow on it gently...
あっ いきなりがっついちゃって かわいいw
Ah, you dove right in, so cute lol
優しく… 丁寧 に、だぞ？
Gentle... and careful, okay?
あはっ… いい子いい子。
Aha... Good boy, good boy.
…お腹、いっぱいになっちゃったね。
You're so full now.
…一緒に、寝ちゃう？
Wanna sleep together?
おやすみなさ～い♪
Good night♪
もしもし キミが シュンとしちゃっても
Even if you're feeling down,
ぎゅってぎゅってぎゅって 抱きしめてあげる
I'll hug you tight, tight, tight.
いくよ マクハリ！
Here we go, Makuhari!
さあさぎゅっどん だぎゅっどん 一緒に食べよう
Come on, gyudon, gyudon, let's eat together.
キミとなんどでも カーニバル！
Carnival with you anytime!
とろとろチューワンは
The torotoro chu-wan is
ホロリお肉 お肉
Horori meat, meat.
つまんじゃダメ
Don't pinch.
全部食べたら 褒めちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you.
なでなで よしよし ちゅー ちゅーちゅー
Nade-nade, yoshi-yoshi, chu-chu-chu.
あぴゃあぴゃ あぴゃあぴゃ
Apya apya apya...
せーの ぎゅっどん！
Ready, gyu-don!
ぎゅどん カーニバル！
Gyudon Carnival!
大好き ぎゅっとしてドン！
Love you, hug and don!
まだまだドン！ みんなと会えるの ぎゅっどん！
Still don! Meeting everyone, gyudon!
ぎゅーーーっ！
Gyu----!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
響咲 リオナ
[Isaki Riona]
虎金妃 笑虎
[Koganei Niko]
水宮 枢
[Mizumiya Su]
輪堂 千速
[Rindo Chihaya]
綺々羅々 ヴィヴィ
[Kikirara Vivi]
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
lock on
目と目がかえれば i know
When our eyes meet, I know
キミこそが相棒
You're my partner
メロつかせる才能 (what ?)
Talent that melts hearts (What?)
(make it ? break it ?)
(Make it? Break it?)
パッと見天使でも (でも)
Even if I look like an angel (Though)
中には潜むデーモン (デーモン)
There's a demon lurking inside (A demon)
so ギャップと愛嬌があれば最強
With the gap and charm, I'm the strongest
hater はシカット
Haters, ignore them
「 へー 、 あっそ ! 」
"Oh, is that so!"
一蓮托生オーガナイズ
A shared destiny, organize
退屈に用はない
We have no use for boredom
一線画すよボーダーライン
We draw the border line
届かない ? しょーがない
Can't reach it? Well, too bad
ウチらが集まればバリ baddest
When we gather, we're the baddest
見惚れ ちゃうでしょ ?
You'll be mesmerized, right?
look at me , look at me now . . .
Look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない絶対
We'll never leave you behind
ついて来て 5mc 's
Come along, 5 MCs
本気のフライデーナイト
Our serious Friday night
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Pierce through me, lean in
夢に強引 going , going on !
Going, going on toward our dreams!
break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け行け
Break right through the center and go
can't get enough
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
ほら 、 どっちにするの ?
Hey, which one will you choose?
有象無象沸かす flow glow
Stirring up the mob, FlowGlow
ay 口先 より 行動
Actions speak louder than words
if you wanna be マイメン
If you wanna be my main
よそ見とかナシ で
No looking away
warning ! 没頭ほら 没頭ほら
Warning! Get immersed, look!
味わいっちゃって
Savor it up
burning ! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Burning! Even hotter, even hotter
ハイになりちゃって
Getting so high
置いてかない絶対
We'll never leave you behind
ついて来て 5mc 's
Come along, 5 MCs
本気のフライデーナイト
Our serious Friday night
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
brand new generation
感じる まま アガれアガれ
Feel it and rise up, rise up
華麗に降臨 only , only one
Gracefully descending, only one
退屈な neverland
Boring Neverland
速攻で抜け出せ i say
Escape instantly, I say
ready or not ?
Ready or not?
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
朝 まで make some noise
Make some noise until morning
make a revolution
アタシを貫け 傾け
Pierce through me, lean in
夢に強引 going , going on !
Going, going on toward our dreams!
break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け行け
Break right through the center and go
can't get enough
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
you'll see !
You'll see!
make it or break it
make it ? break it ?
Make it? Break it?
make it or break it
ほら 、 どっちにするの ?
Hey, which one will you choose?
皆さん私たちのステージ見てくれてありがとうございます！まずはおたちの自己紹介からさせてください！
Thank you all for watching our stage! First, let us introduce ourselves!
まずは私から！
First, from me!
皆さん私がおかえりなさい、おかえりなさい、おかえりなさいって言ったらみんなでただいま「おかえりなさい」って言ってほしいです！
When I say "Welcome back," please reply with "Welcome back"!
そして挨拶の最後のブラブラも「せーの」っていうのでよかったら一緒に言ってください！いいですか？
And for the greeting at the end, please say it with me on "Ready, set"!
せーの！
Ready, set!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
行きます！おかえりなさい、おかえりなさい、おかえりなさい！
Here we go! Welcome back, welcome back, welcome back!
ただいまー！
Welcome back!
ありがとう！おかえり！私の元においで！リョナインドアハウス！フロウグローのリーダー響咲リョナです！せーの！
Thank you! Welcome back! I'm Isaki Riona, leader of FlowGlow! Ready, set!
ブラブラ！ありがとう！めっちゃ嬉しい！
Bula-bula! Thank you! I'm so happy!
もう本当に今ここでみんなと会えたことすごく幸せです！そしてフロウグローの皆とここでステージをこの日を迎えられたことをとても幸せに思います！
I'm truly happy to share this stage and welcome this day with everyone!
今日は一日楽しんでいくぞー！
Let's have fun all day today!
ニコ！いくぞ！ニコたんがー！せーの！来たー！
Niko! Let's go! Niko-tan is—! Ready, set! Here she comes!
ぷらでばいすフロウグローのお笑い担当虎金妃笑虎です！ニコたんないよ！
FlowGlow's comedy representative, Koganei Niko!
あ、嬉しい。ねえ、ニコたんもこれレポってやつやってもいい？
Oh, I'm so happy. Hey, Niki-tan, can I do
やつやってもいい？
one of those report things too?
もちろんだよ！じゃあ、ニコたんわって言ったら、トララだと思う人はトラって言って、人だと思う人は人って言ってください。
Of course! So, when Niki-tan says "Niki-tan, wa...", if you think tiger, say "Tora", and if you think human, say "Hito"!
え？どっちかな？こっちもいい？
Huh? Which one? Is this good too?
オッケー！ニコたんわー！
Okay! Niki-tan, wa—!
人ーーー！
HITOーーー!
お前らとは今日が最後のステージ…
Today is the final stage with you guys...
やだーーー！おわらないでーーー！
Nooooo! Don't end!
そして…
And then...
はい！えっと、す…あ、すーが、しぴしわ、すーの充電って言ったら、
Yes! Um, Su... Ah, when Su says "Su's battery...",
足りてるって言ってください！
say "We've got enough!"
はーい！
Okay!
しぴしわ、すーの充電！
Su's battery...!
足りてないーーー！
Not enoughーーー!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
グローグローもえらいせんでんだと、水瀬すーぜ！嬉しいー！
Glow Glow, you're doing great with PR, Minase Su! So happy!
えらいね。うわ、今日もでっかいです。次、ビビ！
So good. Wow, it's huge today. Next, Bibi!
え？おら！こら！
Huh? Hey! Come on!
トラ！ごめん！トラ！ごめん！
Tora! Sorry! Tora! Sorry!
え、ちょっとこっち？あれ？
Huh, wait, this way? Wait?
本当にもう2個目！ぜったい大丈夫だよ！
Truly the second one! It's totally fine!
はい、では、エンジン全開って言ったら、レッツゴーって言ってください！お願いします！
Okay, then, when I say "Full engine throttle", say "Let's go!" Please!
行きますよ！エンジン全開！
Here we go! Full engine throttle!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
グローグロー！DJ系運転士と人生早です！やったーーー！
Glow Glow! DJ-type driver and fast life! Yayーーー!
はい、皆さん！ビビは、もうわかるよね？みんな！
Yes, everyone! You guys already know Bibi, right, everyone?
ビビがせえのって言ったら、うーんで…
When Bibi says "Ready, set...", say "Uun..."
あ、まちがえた！まちがえた！
Ah, I messed up! I messed up!
爆破りで、おもらしです！
Explosion power, it's a pee accident!
ニコ、今の横練習ね、みんな！そうね、準備バッチリね！
Niki, that was just practice, everyone! Right, preparation is all good!
みんな、声出しできてるかー！
Everyone, are your voices warmed upー!
せーの！うーんで…ビビ！
Ready, set! Uun... Bibi!
みんなありがとー！
Thank you everyoneーーー!
いつもキラキラなききららビビでーす！うわーーー！
Always sparkling, glittering Bibi! Wowーーー!
はい、ということでね、セブンスフェスステージ3が始まりました！2日目の夜になります！いえーーー！
Yes, and so, 7th Fes Stage 3 has begun! It's the night of the second day! Yayーーー!
会いたかったよ、みんな！頭回ってるか？
We wanted to see you, everyone! Is your head spinning?
そしてですね、今回はなんと新しい試みが…はい。あ、でもハッシュタグはその前に。あ、そうですね。
And you know, this time there's a new attempt... Yes. Ah, but hashtags before that. Ah, that's right.
じゃあ、ハッシュタグからいきますか！まずは、ハッシュタグは…
Then, shall we start with the hashtags? First, the hashtag is...
ホロライブフェスEXPO26でいつもです！ね、熱い熱いですよ、普通は。
Hololive Fes EXPO '26, always! Right, it's hot, it's hot, normally.
みんなたくさんポストしてください！
Everyone, please post a lot!
そしてね…はい、じゃあ続いて、あのさっきの、今日…
And you know... Yes, then next, that earlier, today...
今回、とろっことかさね、みんなの客席に来たんだじゃないですか？
This time, we came to everyone's audience seats on trolleys and stuff, right?
近くで見てくれましたか、グローグロースタッフ？ちょっと太もも近すぎた気…
Did you see us up close, Glow Glow staff? I felt my thighs were a bit too close...
ちょっと、皆さんから下から見られる太ももちょっと恥ずかしかったわ！
Wait, having my thighs looked at from below by everyone was a bit embarrassing!
でも太もも最高でした！ビビのお尻もヤバいから！
But thighs were the best! Bibi's butt is crazy too!
だめだめだめ！俺らのステージからなりたい放題…
No no no! Doing whatever we want from our stage...
あと、あと、何？ちょっとニコたんもちょっと…
Also, also, what? Wait, Niki-tan also...
ズルいずるい、そんなんズルい！やめましょうね、一旦元に戻りましょう！
Unfair, unfair, that's so unfair! Let's stop that, let's go back to normal for now!
戻りましょっか！ということで、YouTubeやTikTokでご覧の方は、なんと、ここまでになってしまいます！
Let's go back! So, for those watching on YouTube or TikTok, it ends right here!
ここまでに！
Up to here!
こんな感じでね、なってる方はですね、ぜひあの概要欄からあの配信チケット買えますのでね、こういうふうになっちゃって、しまってる方はぜひあのよろしくお願いします！
For those who ended up like this, you can buy streaming tickets from the description below, so if you ended up like this, please check it out!
そしてですね、このあとね、5人で合流するところも見れないわけでしょう！
And you know, after this, you won't be able to see the 5 of us merging together either!
いやだいやだ、やらない！やらないからね！ということでね、ま、ここまあとゆことで、最後に私たちもじゃあ合流するということで…
No way, no way, I won't! I won't do it! So, up to here, and finally we will also merge...
会場の皆さんとも最後に、会場の皆さんとね、合流していきたいと思うんですけど…
At the end, we want to merge with everyone at the venue too...
一つになろうね！
Let's become one!
ということで、なんと私達のお願いがあります！私たちここを5分割ぐらいかな？目の前のメンバーにペンライトの色を変えてもらうことってできたりしますか？
So, we have a request! Can we divide ourselves into about 5 parts? Can you have the audience change their penlight colors to match the member in front of them?
ひとり！ お願いします！
Everyone, please!
綺麗だねー！
It's so beautiful!
いや、やっぱり私たちもフェスに出れたということで
Yeah, after all, since we were able to make it to Fes,
先輩たちがいつもやってるウェーブやりたいよね！
we want to do the wave our seniors always do!
じゃあ私から運用していくから
So I'll start the wave,
下がるべ…上がればいい？
Do we go down? Or up?
こうやって下がって、上がって…走るんだよね！
Like this, go down, go up... and run!
私たちがいるところを「いー」ってやってもらうとみんな慣れてるよね！
If you say "ee" where we are, everyone is used to it!
あっちから、ゆっくりね！あっちに向かって走ろうよ！
From that side, slowly! Let's run toward that side!
あっちから、ピンクの色の色からですよ！
From that side, starting from the pink color!
あ、ピンクの色の色からね！じゃあ行きますよ！
Ah, starting from the pink color! Then let's go!
はい、せーの！ ぴんぴんぴん！
Ready, set! Pin-pin-pin!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで幸せな時間はありがとうございました！
With that, thank you very much for this wonderful time!
じゃあ最後のキメ台詞、いきますか！
Well then, shall we do our final signature catchphrase?
いきまーす！
Let's go!
じゃあみんな魂込めて、今日の想いを全て込めて言いましょ！
Everyone, put your soul and all your feelings from today into it as we say it!
ライディオーン！ ドリームズ！
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.